(Sheldon:)Penny?
(grunts)
(Penny:)Ugh, what?
(Sheldon:)You sounded in distress.
(Sheldon:)I was worried something
unpleasant was happening to you.
(Sheldon:)Like a murder.
(Sheldon:)Or spontaneous coitus
with Leonard.
(Penny:)Oh, I'm just doing
this awful workout.
(Penny:)I hate it.
(Sheldon:)Well, if you hate it,
then why are you doing it?
(Sheldon:)Although I could ask
the same question
(Sheldon:)about coitus with Leonard.
(Penny:)I don't know-- I guess
I like that I hate it.
(Penny:)It makes me work harder.
(Sheldon:)And to clarify...
(Penny:)The exercise, Sheldon.
(Penny:)Shouldn't you be getting
ready for work?
(Sheldon:)I'm not going.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to know why?
(Penny:)Uh, you're sad about not getting
anything done last night,
(Penny:)so you're gonna sit around
and pout about it?
(Sheldon:)Boy, I'm not nearly as
mysterious as I think I am.
(Howard:)I invented a game.
(Howard:)You want to play?
Sure.
(Howard:)It's called
"Emily or Cinnamon?"
(Howard:)I give you actual quotes
I've heard Raj say,
(Howard:)and you guess if he was talking
to his girlfriend or his dog.